



Education

2015-08 -2017-12 Ohio State University

B.A in Journalism, Minor in International Relations & Foreign Diplomacy GPA: 3.2

2014-08 -2015-05 Colby College

Majored in Biochemistry GPA:3.4

Transfered



Experience

2017 present **Marketing Intern**

Brandt-Roberts Galleries

- · Assisted with the editorials, press releases and newsletter
- · Responsible for managing social media posting on Facebook and Instagram
- · Composed digital show invitations to the gallery clients and artists

2016-09 -2017-05 Reporter

Lantern, the student newspaper

- Responsible for interviewing current news subjects that were associated with Ohio State University
- · Accomplished thirteen news stories in a semester
- Produced videos and photographies for my stories

2015 -2017 Freelance Writer

College Daily

- Responsible for interviewing news subjects involved in current events that triggers an interest for general college students
- · Actively Involved in more than 20 stories
- Able to obtain a high volume of digital traffic, an average of 50,000 clicks each article.



Additional Experience

2016 present Facility Assistant

Recreation & Physical Activity Center

- Monitored daily facility schedule
- Gained leadership experience training new employees.
- Assisted with developing and executing policies for effective facility management

2015-11 -2016-11 **Wexner Medical Center**

Student Assistant

- Served food for patients and medical staff
- Talked to patients and accommodated their nutritional needs
- Actively worked on improving their dinning experiences



Professional References

Michelle Brandt, Brandt-Roberts Galleries, Business Owner

642 N. High Street. Columbus. Ohio, 43215

Phone: 614 – 223- 1655

E-mail: info@brandtrobertsgalleries.com Relationship: Internship Supervisor

Spencer Hunt, Director of The Lantern, Ohio State University

271 Journalism Building, 242 W 18th Avenue

614-247-7030

Email: hunt.754@osu.edu

Relationship: Lantern Media Director

Personal Info

Address

571 Stinchcomb Drive. Columbus, Ohio. 43202

Phone

(207)-313-0672

E-mail

yutingyangosu@gmail.com



Summary

A recent OSU graduate with 2 years experiences freelancing and social media management, motivated and detail-oriented, proficient at composing media content as well as generating multi-media for marketing purposes, seeking to contribute my communication skills and journalism expertise to your team.



Communication

Advanced

Writing Skills



Teamwork





Final Cut/ iMovie



Photoshop



Dreamweaver (HTML)



Microsoft/ Excel

